[When I press the hotkey:]
When I press the hotkey:
[BossKey: Key pressed]
BossKey: Key pressed
[Change only if current status is Online]
Change only if current status is Online
[When I return:]
When I return:
[Hide Miranda if the computer is locked]
Hide Miranda if the computer is locked
[Hotkey:]
Hotkey:
[BossKey]
BossKey
[BossKey: Hide/Show Miranda]
BossKey: Hide/Show Miranda
[Use default status message]
Use default status message
[Request password:]
Request password:
[BossKey: Miranda is hidden]
BossKey: Miranda is hidden
[Change status to]
Change status to
[Change status back]
Change status back
[Create a main menu item]
Create a main menu item
[Disable Sounds]
Disable Sounds
[Go to Customize -> Hotkeys to change hotkey.]
Go to Customize -> Hotkeys to change hotkey.
[Use built in to Miranda hotkey module]
Use built in to Miranda hotkey module
[Show the Tray Icon]
Show the Tray Icon
